guerillastocktrading.com 2016-12-31

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for http://www.GuerillaStockTrading.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.

If you subscribe to this blog, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. 

**Updates**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page. 

**Cookies**

We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. 

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

**Links**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

### Top Performing GuerillaStockTrading Picks For Week Ending December 30 2016

### STOCK MARKET PREDICTION SHOW OVER 24,000 SUBSCRIBERS!

### Disclosure Statement

We are a professional website that receives compensation from the companies whose products we review and recommend. We are independently owned and the opinions we express here are our own. We have high standards and a reputation to uphold. Our recommendations are researched carefully and if the company or companies we currently recommend do not maintain their high quality of service, we will take appropriate action including updating this website to reflect any necessary changes.

The information on this website is for informational purposes only. DO NOT BASE ANY INVESTMENT DECISION UPON ANY MATERIALS FOUND ON THIS WEBSITE. We are not registered as a securities broker-dealer or an investment adviser either with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (the SEC) or with any state securities regulatory authority. We are neither licensed nor qualified to provide investment advice. The contents of this website are not provided to any particular individual with a view toward their individual circumstances. You should seek advice from a licensed and registered investment adviser for your particular situation.
